圣诞前夜
'Twas the night before Christmas!
公园之中
And all through the park...
你们在说啥  嘿  约翰尼  为啥圣诞树还不亮
There are a bunch of people saying "hey, Johnny, why's that tree still dark?"
怎么回事哈
- Huh? - [Applause]
好咧  伙计们  演出开始前
All right, folks. Well, before our big show-stopping solo,
丽芙鲁尼将要为我们点亮这棵圣诞树
Liv Rooney has the honor of lighting that tree.
不如我们把她叫出来  来
So let's get her out here, huh? Come on.
谢谢你  约翰  能由我来点亮这棵树真是个荣幸
Thank you, Johnny. Lighting this tree is a great honor...
现在我想要把这个荣幸给一个及其年轻的
But it is one that I would like to pass on to the young and...
及其出色的小甜心  珍妮肯恩
Very talented Jenny Keene.
欢迎她
This is her moment.
也许珍妮需要一个真正关心她的人
Maybe all Jenny needed was that one person to truly care about her
引导她走向至善至美呢
so that she could blossom into the greatest version of herself.
给我走开  你这个金发女
Get off my stage, blondie.
好吧  也许是我错了
Okay. Maybe not.
圣诞快乐  斯蒂文伯恩斯的人们
Merry Christmas, Stevens Point.
太好了
Ha! Yes!
哈哈
Ha ha.
呃  爸爸  这东西是这么冒烟的吗
Uh, Dad, is that supposed to be smoking like that?
呃  好像珍妮肯恩把圣诞节毁得渣都不剩了
Well, it looks like little Jenny Keene just ruined Christmas.
圣诞树完蛋了  圣诞树完蛋了
Christmas Tree down. Christmas Tree down!
丽芙鲁尼  你耍我
Liv Rooney, you set me up!
这个女人毁了我的大好时刻
She ruined my big moment.
我恨这个镇子  我恨你们所有人
I hate this town, and everyone in it!
女士们先生们
And that, ladies and gentlemen...
刚刚其实是珍妮肯恩在模仿埃比尼泽“吝啬鬼”啦  不要介意哈
Was little Jenny Keene's impression of Ebenezer Scrooge.
耶  珍妮
Yay, Jenny. [Chuckles]
多么有才华横溢的小演员啊  不是吗
Oh, what a talented little actress, am I right?
我猜今天的表演就是这样了  吧
So that's probably it for the show.
还是该来一句圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas?
哇
Oh. Wow.
她还真是个小魔鬼
She really is a monster.
是啊  我早跟你说过了好吗妈妈  她比我小时候要糟糕几百倍呢
Yeah, I told you, Mom. She is way worse than I was.
记住今天可是圣诞节哦亲爱的
It's Christmas, Sweetie. Sure.
嗯  结束了  都结束了
Well, I guess the show's over.
失败  不能更失败了   哦  亲爱的亲爱的  我知道  妈妈
- It's a bummer. - Oh, I know, honey. I was...
妈妈真的真的很期待很期待你的表演的哦
I was really looking forward to your big solo.
好戏在后头呢
Don't give up yet.
我和老爸要拯救这个圣诞节了
I think Dad and I may have actually found a way to save Christmas.
你们就准备好吧  过一个没电圣诞
Get ready for "Christmas unplugged".
丽芙就可以唱《下雪吧》
And Liv gets to sing "let it snow".
唯一的一首歌对吧
That is the only song you'll be singing, right?
哦  外面的天气真可怕
Oh, the weather outside is frightful.
但是屋里的炉火好温馨
But the fire is so delightful.
既然我们没有地方可去
And since we've no place to go...
就下雪吧  下雪吧  下雪吧
Let it snow, let it snow. Let it snow.
雪好像没有要停的征兆
Oh, it doesn't show signs of stopping.
正好可以爆爆米花
And I've bought some corn for popping.
把灯光调暗  好好感受这温馨
The lights are turned way down low.
下雪吧  下雪吧  下雪吧
Let it snow, let it snow. Let it snow...
虽然没下雪  但是貌似是最棒的一个圣诞了哈
Even though it didn't snow, it's kind of the perfect Christmas Eve, huh?
是的  除了我把模型机给搞破掉了
Yeah, except I already broke my helicopter.
你还有个后备啊
Well, at least you have a backup.
没啦  那个也寿终正寝了
Nope, broke that one too.
回家的一路上  我都会很温暖
All the way home I'll be warm.
火苗漫漫熄灭
The fire is slowly dying.
亲爱的们  再见咯
And my dear, we're still goodbye-ing.
只要你们爱我
But as long as you love me so.
就会下雪
Let it snow, let it snow. Let it snow.
好咧大伙  再见各位
All right, listen. Good night, everybody.
没下雪  不过还好至少没下雨对吧
I know it didn't snow, but at least it didn't rain, right?
开什么玩笑啊
Are you kidding me?